A Guide to the Ann A. Hertzler Collection, 1863-2013 (Bulk 1974-2000)
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Series II: Hertzler Publications, 1971-2000
  - Subseries A: Articles, 1966-2001
    - Articles, 1991-1995 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      Minish, Roberta, Ann A. Hertzler, and Robert B. Frary. "Transferable Job Skills for Current and Future Employment of Food and Nutrition Alumni: An Exploratory Study." Topics in Clinical Nutrition 8, no 4. (September 1993): 83-89.
      Hertzler, Ann A., Ginger A. Veazey, and Mary Pat Ward. "Food Interviewing Activity." Journal of Nutrition Education 25, no. 294D (1993): np.
      Hertzler, Ann A., Ryland Webb, and Robert B. Frary. "Over Consumption of Fat by College Students: The Fast Food Connection." Ecology of Food and Nutrition 34 (1995): 49-57.
      Hertzler, Ann A. and Robert B. Frary. "A Dietary Calcium Rapid Assessment Method (RAM)." Topics in Clinical Nutrition 9, no. 3 (June 1994): 76-85.
      Carlson, Barbara B. and Ann A. Herzler. "A Comparison of Food Guides." Journal of Nutrition in Recipe & Menu Development 1, no. 3 (1995): 3-13
      Hertzler, Ann A., Kathleen M. Stadler, Ramona Lawrence, Lisa A. Alleyne, Lynn D. Mattioli, and Maryam Majidy. "Empowerment: A Food Guidenace Process for Cross-Cultural Counseling." Journal of Family and Consumer Sciences 87, no. 2 (Summer 1995): 45-50.
      Hertzler, Ann A., and Robert B. Frary. "College Students' Nutrition Information Networks." Family and Consumer Sciences Research Journal 24, no. 2 (December 1995): 191-202.
      Stadler, Kathleen M., and Ann A. Hertzler. "Sensory, Academic, and Creative Nutrition Education Activities for Preschoolers." Journal of Nutrition Education 27, no. 107A (1995): np.
    - Articles, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Amend, Christa, Ann A. Hertzler, Ryland E. Webb, and Patrick J. McCarthy. "A Food Checklist for Rapid Assessement of Energy and Protein." Journal of Nutrition in Recipe & Menu Development 2, no. 3 (1996): 3-11.
      Hertzler, Ann A., and Rovbert B. Frary. "Family Factors and Fat Consumption of College Students." Journal of the American Dietetic Association 96, no. 7 (July 1996): 711-714.
      Hertzler, Ann A. "Food Guides: Programs and Policies." Journal of Family and Consumer Sciences 88, no. 2 (Summer 1996): 26-32.
      Hertzler, Ann A., and Juanita Bowens. "Educating Volunteers to Maximize Health Fair Outcomes." Journal of Family and Consumer Sciences 88, no. 3 (Fall 1996): 48-50.
      Hertzler, Ann A., Robert B. Frary, and Candice L. Ward. "Food Guide Pyramid Menus for Preschoolers--Adequacy of Selected Nutrients." Journal of Family and Consumer Sciences 88, no. 4 (Winter 1996): 63-65.
      Colavito, Elizabeth A., Joanne F. Guthrie, Ann A. Hertzler, and Ryland E. Webb. "Relationship of Diet-Health Attitudes and Nutrition Knowledge of Household Meal Planners to the Fat and Fiber Intakes of Meal Planners and Preschoolers." Journal of Nutrition Education 28, no. 6 (November/December 1996): 321-328.
      Hertzler, Ann A. "Managing Food and Nutrition Resources: Paradigm Shift for the 21st Century." In Family Resource Management Issues, 31-36. Paris: Family Resource management Committee, International Federation for Home Economics, 1996.
    - Articles, 1998-2001 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      Hertzler, Ann A., Michael Leahy, and Chris Colvin. "Food Choice Computer Program." Journal for the Study of Food and Society 2, no. 1 (Spring 1998): 37-41.
      Hertzler, Ann A., and Susan Murphy. "We Eat What We Read." Nutrition Link 21, no. 1 (June 1998): 1-4.
      Plum, Jane, Ann A. Hertzler, Denise Brochetti, and Daisy Stewart. "Game to Asses Nutrion Concepts of Preschool Children." Journal of the American Dietetic Association 98, no. 10 (October 1998): 1168-1171.
      Hertzler, Ann A., and Robert B. Frary. "Preschool Children's Food Problems and Food-Related Caregiving Techniques." Journal of Consumer Studies & Home Economics 23, no. 3 (September 1999): 147-154.
      Hertzler, Ann A., and Robert B. Frary. "Dietary Guidelines--A Self-Assessment." Journal of Consumer Studies & Home Economics 23, no. 3 (September 1999): 155-160.
      Hertzler, Ann A., Virginia E. Young, Christina M. Baum, Misty Lawson, and Michelle Penn-Marshall. "Nutrition and Exercise Information for Children on the Internet." Journal of Family and Consumer Sciences 91. no. 3 (1999): 100-103.
      Hertzler, Ann A. "'Nourishing Books' for Young Children." Topics in Clinical Nutrition 15, no. 3 (2000): 28-34.
      Hertzler, Ann A., and Susan R. Hutchinson. "One Size Does Not Fill All in Obesity Research." Journal of the American Dietetic Association 100, no. 8 (August 2000): 883.
      Hertzler, Ann A., and Susan R. Hutchinson. "Parental Eating Messages and Dietary Guideline Compliance of College Students." Journal of Consumer Studies & Home Economics 24, no. 3 (September 2000): 139-144.
      Wu, Yi-Ping, Ann A. Hertzler, and Shirley M. Miller. "Vitamin A, Vitamin C, Calcium, and Iron Content of Federally Funded Preschool Lunches in Virginia." Journal of the American Dietetic Association 101, no. 3 (March 2001): 348-351.
  - Subseries B: Contributions, 1976-2001
    - Articles, Quoted, 1983-2001 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Bellamy Newsletter Research Files (Box 14, Folder 1-2 (2 folders))
    - Books, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Pamphlets, 1976-1996, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Presentation Materials, 1982-1995 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Presentation Materials, 1996-2000 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Subseries C: University of Missouri-Columbia Extension, 1971-1974, n.d.
    - Dated Publications, 1971-1974 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Hertzler, Ann. "Nutrition Newsletter." January 1971-April/May 1973.
      Hertzler, Ann. "Teaching Nutrition to Youth." January 1971-April/May 1973.
      "Nutritous Snacks." EFNEP Conference, 1973.
      "The Food Curriculum." January 1974. Associated presentation slides available online.
    - "Home Economics Guides" Series (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Hertzler, Ann A. Biscuits: Judging Quick Breads, no. 1222. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Hertzler, Ann. Muffins and Pastry: Judging Quick Breads, no. 1223. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Hertzler, Ann A. The Art of Making Biscuits, no. 1221. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Hertzler, Ann. Thickening Sauces and Gravies with Starch, no. 1283. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Hertzler, Ann. Preventing Lumps in Sauces Thickened with Starch, no. 1284. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Hertzler, Ann, and Viola Smith. Garnishes: Tricks with Trims, no. 1290. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Hertzler, Ann A. Herbs and Spices, no. 1297. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Hertzler, Ann, and William Stringer. Meat Selection, no. 1582. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Hertzler, Ann. Homemade Baby Foods, no. 1741. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Hertzler, Ann A. Breast Milk and Milk Formulas, no. 1742. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Hertzler, Ann A. What to Feed Babies After Milk, no. 1743. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Hertzler, Ann. Nutrition and Pregnancy, no. 1781. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Hertzler, Ann A. Break-Fast, no. 1830. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Hertzler, Ann A., and Yolonda Enyart. Teaching about Breakfast, no. 1832. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Hertzler, Ann A. Food Comparison Charts for Teenage Girls and Women, no. 1861. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Hertzler, Ann A. Food Comparison Charts for Infants and Children, no. 1862. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Hertzler, Ann A. Iron in the Body, no. 1902. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Hertzler, Ann A. Recommended Dietary Allowances, no. 1903. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Hertzler, Ann. Vitamin C in the Body, no. 1905. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Hertzler, Ann A. Vitamin D in the Body, no. 1906. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Hertzler, Ann A. Vitamin E in the Body, no. 1907. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Hertzler, Ann. Vitamin K in the Body, no. 1908. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Hertzler, Ann A. Iodine in the Body, no. 1909. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Hertzler, Ann A. Nutrients in Processed Fruits and Vegetables, no. 1910. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Hertzler, Ann. Breads and Flours, no. 1911. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Dowdy, Richard. Zinc in the Body, no. 1912. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Hertzler, Ann, and Marion Cloninger. How Bacteria Grow, no. 1971. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Hertzler, Ann, and Helen Anderson. How Animals Grow, no. 1972. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Hertzler, Ann, and Laurel Anderson. How Seeds Grow, no. 1975. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Hertzler, Ann A., and Roy W. Allison. Purple Cabbage Indicator: Testing for Acidity and Alkalinity, no. 1977. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Hertzler, Ann, and Marilyn Caselman. Suggestions for Demonstrations, no. 1978. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Hertzler, Ann, and Marilyn Caselman. Demonstrations in Food and Nutrition, no. 1979. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Willenberg, Barbara, and Ann A. Hertzler. Snacks for Children. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
    - Undated Publications (MP Series) (Box 2, Folder 5)
      Kitchen Tips: Use What You Have on Hand, MP206. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Wilson, Lorene, and Ann Herzler. Shopping Hints for Turkey, MP282. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Wilson, Lorene, and Ann Herzler. Shopping Hints for Liver, MP284. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Wilson, Lorene, and Ann Herzler. Shopping Hints for Snacks, MP291. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Wilson, Lorene, and Ann Herzler. Shopping Hints for Bread, MP292. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Wilson, Lorene, and Ann Herzler. Shopping Hints for Cheese, MP293. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Wilson, Lorene, and Ann Herzler. Shopping Hints for Milk, MP294. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Wilson, Lorene, and Ann Herzler. Shopping Hints for Dried Beans, Dried Peas, & Nuts, MP295. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Hertzler, Ann A. So You Want to Know?, MP439. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Hertzler, Ann, and Dorothy Wagner. Rudy and Iron, MP 496. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division. (3 copies) Available online.
      Hertzler, Ann, and Phyllis Pirner. Susie and Calcium, MP 512. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division. (2 copies) Available online.
      Hertzler, Ann, and Phyllis Pirner. Andy and Vitamin A, MP 513. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division. (2 copies) Available online.
      Hertzler, Ann, and Phyllis Pirner. Cindy and Vitamin C, MP 514. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division. (2 copies) Available online.
    - Undated Publications (Y Series and Unidentified) (Box 2, Folder 6)
      Bibliography - Y Series
      Hertzler, Ann, Pat Lieurance, Charline Lindsay, and Viola Smith. It's Cookout Time, Leader's Guide 254. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension.
      Hertzler, Ann, Pat Lieurance, Charline Lindsay, and Viola Smith. It's Cookout Time, Member's Manual Y254. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension.
      Lindsay, Charline. Food for Special Events, Leader's Guide Y257. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension.
      Hertzler, Ann. Food and You: Discovering 4-H, Leader's Supplement Y950. University of Missouri-Columbia Extension Division.
      Bibliography - Unidentified
      "Corn Syrup-- Recipes and Hints."
      O'Neal, Robert, Dorothy Wagner, and Ann Hertzler. Iron for Everyone. Columbia, MO: Lincoln University Cooperative Extension Service. (Photocopies)
      "Nonfat Dry Milk in Family Meals."
      "Tips to Help Measure Up."
    - Iron for Everyone Cards (2 copies) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Subseries D: Virgina Cooperative Extension (VCE)/Adult, 1982-2000
    - VCE/Adults, 1982-1995 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Hertzler, Ann A., and Phyllis Brown. February 1982. Cookouts and Cooking While Camping, Publication 348-010. [Blacksburg, Va.]: Virginia Cooperative Extension. Available online.
      Hertzler, Ann A. February 1982. Nutritious Carried Meals, Publication 348-015. [Blacksburg, Va.]: Virginia Cooperative Extension.
      Hertzler, Ann A. May 1984. Fat in Your Diet, Publication 348-908. [Blacksburg, Va.]: Virginia Cooperative Extension.
      Hertzler, Ann A. May 1984. Potassium in the Diet, Publication 348-911. [Blacksburg, Va.]: Virginia Cooperative Extension. Available online.
      Hertzler, Ann A. March 1985. Safe Carried Meals, Publication 348-016. [Blacksburg, Va.]: Virginia Cooperative Extension. Later revision available online.
      Hertzler, Ann A. February 1986. Fiber in the Diet, Publication 348-912. [Blacksburg, Va.]: Virginia Cooperative Extension.
      Hertzler, Ann A. May 1986. Herbs and Spices, Publication 348-907. [Blacksburg, Va.]: Virginia Cooperative Extension.
      Hertzler, Ann A. January 1987. Cholesterol in the Diet, Publication 348-909. [Blacksburg, Va.]: Virginia Cooperative Extension. Available online.
      Hertzler, Ann A. April 1987. Fat in Your Diet, Publication 348-908. [Blacksburg, Va.]: Virginia Cooperative Extension. Available online.
      Hertzler, Ann A. July 1987. Fiber in the Diet, Publication 348-912. [Blacksburg, Va.]: Virginia Cooperative Extension. Available online.
      Hertzler, Ann A. August 1987. Sodium in the Diet, Publication 348-910. [Blacksburg, Va.]: Virginia Cooperative Extension. Available online.
      Hertzler, Ann A. 1988. The Four Food Groups: Food for Fitness, Publication 348-906. [Blacksburg, Va.]: Virginia Cooperative Extension.
      Hertzler, Ann A. 1993. Sugar, Publication 348-013. [Blacksburg, Va.]: Virginia Cooperative Extension.
      Hertzler, Ann, and Denise Brochetti. 1995. Food Cents, Publication 348-006. [Blacksburg, Va.]: Virginia Cooperative Extension. Available online.
      Hertzler, Ann A. 1995. Planning Carried Meals, Publication 348-014. [Blacksburg, Va.]: Virginia Cooperative Extension.
    - VCE/Adults, 1996-2000 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Hertzler, Ann A. 1996. Iron Check List, Publication 348-371. [Blacksburg, Va.]: Virginia Cooperative Extension. Later revision available online.
      Hertzler, Ann A. 1997. Herbs and Spices, Publication 348-907. [Blacksburg, Va.]: Virginia Cooperative Extension. 2001 reprint available online.
      Hertzler, Ann A. 1997. Fat Tracker, Publication 348-900. [Blacksburg, Va.]: Virginia Cooperative Extension.
      Hertzler, Ann A. 1998. Calcium Checklist - Food Guide Pyramid, Publication 348-019. [Blacksburg, Va.]: Virginia Cooperative Extension. Available online.
      Hertzler, Ann A. 1999. Planning for Carried Meals, Publication 348-014. [Blacksburg, Va.]: Virginia Cooperative Extension. Available online.
      Hertzler, Ann A. 2000. Calcium Checklist - Food Guide Pyramid, Publication 348-019. [Blacksburg, Va.]: Virginia Cooperative Extension.
  - Subseries E: Virgina Cooperative Extension (VCE)/Children, 1985-1999
    - VCE/Children, 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Hertzler, Ann A. April 1984. Preschoolers' Food Handling Skills-Motor Development, Publication 348-011. [Blacksburg, Va.]: Virginia Cooperative Extension. Available online.
      Hertzler, Ann A. March 1985. Homemade Baby Food, Publication 348-012. [Blacksburg, Va.]: Virginia Cooperative Extension. Available online.
      Hertzler, Ann A. October 1987. Kids, Food, and Money, Publication 348-007. [Blacksburg, Va.]: Virginia Cooperative Extension. Available online.
      Hertzler, Ann, Valya Vincell, Janet Tuckwiller, Kathleen Stadler, Katherine Sharman, and Martha Durst. 1988. Let's Start Eating Smart, Publication 348-650. [Blacksburg, Va.]: Virginia Cooperative Extension. Available online.
    - VCE/Children, 1993-1999 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      Hertzler, Ann A., Mick Coleman, and Elaine D. Scott. 1993. Kids, Food, and Television, Publication 348-008. [Blacksburg, Va.]: Virginia Cooperative Extension. Available online.
      Debord, Karen, and Ann A. Hertzler. 1993. Developmentally Appropriate Food and Nutrition Skills for Young Children, Publication 348-651. [Blacksburg, Va.]: Virginia Cooperative Extension. Available online.
      Hertzler, Ann A., and Karen DeBord. 1993. Kids Cart Smart Food Choices at Home, Shopping, and Eating Out, Publication 348-652. [Blacksburg, Va.]: Virginia Cooperative Extension. Available online.
      Hertzler, Ann A., and Karen DeBord. 1993. Germ Squirm: Kids and Safe Food Handling, Publication 348-653. [Blacksburg, Va.]: Virginia Cooperative Extension. Available online.
      Hertzler, Ann A., and Karen DeBord. 1993. Health Wealth: Kinds, Nutrients, and Health, Publication 348-654. [Blacksburg, Va.]: Virginia Cooperative Extension.
      Hertzler, Ann A., and Karen DeBord. 1993. Hurts and Hazards: Kids, Kitchen Accidents, and Safety, Publication 348-655. [Blacksburg, Va.]: Virginia Cooperative Extension. Available online.
      Hertzler, Ann A. 1995. ABC's of Feeding Preschoolers, Publication 348-009. [Blacksburg, Va.]: Virginia Cooperative Extension. Available online.
      Hertzler, Ann A. 1995. Preschoolers' Food Handling Skills-Motor Development, Publication 348-011. [Blacksburg, Va.]: Virginia Cooperative Extension. Available online.
      Hertzler, Ann A., and Karen DeBord. 1996. Health Wealth: Kinds, Nutrients, and Health, Publication 348-654. [Blacksburg, Va.]: Virginia Cooperative Extension. Available online.
      Hertzler, Ann. 1999. Nourishing Children with Books, Publication 348-950. [Blacksburg, Va.]: Virginia Cooperative Extension. Available online.
  - Subseries F: Websites and Internet Resources, 1997-2001 (Box 3, Folder 1-2 (2 folders))
- Series III: Other Publications, 1956-2000
  - Subseries A: Articles and Reports, 1956-1998
    - Articles and Reports, 1956-1979 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Bylund, H. Bruce, and Ralph L. Baker. 1956. Community Program to Increase Egg Consumption. University Park, Pa: Pennsylvania State University, College of Agriculture, Agricultural Experiment Station.
      Bylund, H. Bruce, and Ralph L. Baker. 1956. Effectiveness of Techniques Used in a Better Breakfast Program. University Park, Pa: Pennsylvania State University, College of Agriculture, Agricultural Experiment Station.
      Bylund, H. Bruce, and Ralph L. Baker. 1957. Long Run Effects of a Better Breakfast Program. University Park, Pa: Pennsylvania State University, College of Agriculture, Agricultural Experiment Station.
      Fisher, Katherine H., and H. Bruce Byland. 1957. The Child's Viewpoint on Breakfast. University Park, Pa: Pennsylvania State University, College of Agriculture, Agricultural Experiment Station.
      Cereal Institute (Chicago, Ill.). 1957. A Summary of the Iowa Breakfast Studies.
      Cereal Institute (Chicago, Ill.). 1966. Breakfast Source Book.
      Cereal Institute (Chicago, Ill.). 1969. Better Breakfast Activities.
      Kallen, David J. "Nutrition and Society." Journal of the American Medical Association 215, no. 1 (January 1971): 94-100.
      Hayde, Eugene B. "Breakfast and Today's Lifestyles." Journal of School Health 45, no. 2 (February 1975): 83-87.
      General Mills Nutrition Department. 1976. Cereal in Today's Changeing Lifestyles.
      Nutrition Action 6, no. 4 (April 1979).
    - Articles and Reports, 1981-1998 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Pollitt, Ernesto, Rudolph L. Leibel, and Daryl Greenfield. "Brief Fasting, Stress, and Cognition in Children." The American Journal of Clinical Nutrition 34 (August 1981): 1526-1533.
      Brun, Judy, and Jane Voichick. 1984. An Inventory of Nutrition Education Evaluation Instruments. [Oakland, Calif.]: The Society.
      School Breakfast Programs: Energizing the Classroom. 1997. St. Paul, Minnesota: Minnesota Department of Children, Families & Learning.
  - Subseries B: Extension Services, 1979-1993 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Kendall, Patricia A., and Willene Dilsaver. 1978. High Altitude Baking. Fort Collins: Cooperative Extension Service, Colorado State University.
    University of Massachusetts (Amherst campus). 1992. The Good Eating for Less Cookbook. [Massachusetts]: University of Massachusetts, Cooperative Extension System.
    Redlinger, Patricia, Diane Nelson, and Valerie King. 1993. Altering Recipes for Health. Ames, Iowa: Iowa State University, University Extension.
  - Subseries C: Pamphlets, 1965-1992, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Dept. of Home Economics and Office of Foreign Study Programs. 1965. "Children and Nutrition Around the World." Dekalb, Ill.: Northern Illinois University.
    Davis, Thomas R. A., and W. H. Sebrell. 1966. The Dietary Role of Cereals in the United States. Chicago: Cereal Institute.
    American Heart Association. 1969. Sodium Restricted Diet: 500 Milligrams. Dallas, Tex: American Heart Association.
    American Heart Association. 1969. Sodium Restricted Diet: Mild Restriction. Dallas, Tex: American Heart Association.
    American Heart Association. 1970. Sodium Restricted Diet: 1000 Milligrams. Dallas, Tex: American Heart Association.
    Kellogg Company. 1980. Ready-to-Eat Cereals and Nutrition. Battle Creek, MI: Kellog Company.
    Virginia Dietetic Association. 1981. Making the Most of Your Food Dollar.
    What You Should Know About--Monosodium Glutamate. 1991. Washington, DC: International Food Information Council.
    IFIC: International Food Information Council. 1991. Washington, DC: International Food Information Council.
    National Live Stock and Meat Board. 1992. Food Guide Pyramid: A Guide to Daily Food Choices. Chicago, IL: Education Dept., National Live Stock and Meat Board.
    American Dental Association. "I'm Going to the Dentist." Chicago: American Dental Association.
    Spice Islands. "The Spice Islands Herb & Spice Primer."
    Activity Pyramid
  - Subseries D: USDA, 1960-2000 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    United States. 1960. Food for Families with School Children. Washington: U.S. Dept. of Agriculture.
    United States. 1964. Food for the Family with Young Children. Home and garden bulletin, no. 13. Washington: U.S. Dept. of Agriculture.
    United States. 1970. A Menu Planning Guide for Breakfast at School. Home and garden bulletin, no. 5. Washington: U.S. Dept. of Agriculture, Food and Nutrition Service, Child Nutrition Division.
    Pecot, Rebecca K., and Bernice K. Watt. 1970. Food Yields: Summarized by Different Stages of Preparation. Agricultural Handbook no. 102. Washington, D.C.: Agricultural Research Service, U.S. Dept. of Agriculture.
    United States. 1972. Eat a Good Breakfast to Start a Good Day. Leaflet No. 268. Washington: U.S. Dept. of Agriculture.
    United States. 1980. The Sodium Content of Your Food. Home and garden bulletin, no. 233. Washington: U.S. Dept. of Agriculture.
    United States. 1982. Sodium: Think About It.... Home and garden bulletin, no. 237. Washington: U.S. Dept. of Agriculture.
    United States. 2000. Nutrition and Your Health: Dietary Guidelines for Americans. Home and garden bulletin, no. 232. [Washington, DC]: U.S. Dept. of Agriculture.
- Series IV: Project/Subject Files, 1982-2013